Guide to the New York State College of Agriculture. Department of Agricultural Economics records, 1892-1988
New York State College of Agriculture. Department of Agricultural Economics records, 1892-1988
- Justice School - 1939-1941, 1946; Supervisor's School (Syracuse University) 1940, 1958, 1964, 1939-1964 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Temporary State Commission on the Constitutional Convention, 1955-1966 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Temporary State Commission on the Constitutional Convention, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Tax Collection - New York State, 1932-1943 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Government Finance - Taxation - Property Tax - New York Farm Taxes, 1948-1955 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Government Finance - Sales Tax - New York, 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Highways - New York, 1935-1954 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Political Subdivisions - City Government, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Home Rule, 1936-1967 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Government Finance - General, 1938-1965 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Budget - Towns in New York State, 1940-1952 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- State Aid - Moore Plan, 1945-1963 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- State Aid - Moore Plan, 1963-1974 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Taxation - New York State, 1974-1980 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Property Taxes - New York State, 1974-1980 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Property Taxes - Assessment - New York State, 1941-1963 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Property Taxes, Assessment - Tompkins Co., Town of Ulysses, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Assessment Improvement Law, 1968-1970 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Constitutional Convention - Local Finance - Amendments, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Constitutional Convention - Discussions, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Constitutional Convention - Correspondence/memos, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Constitutional Convention - Discussions, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Constitutional Convention - Correspondence/memos, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Constitutional Convention - Explanation of Proposals, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Constitutional Convention - Citizens Union - recommendations, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Project Statements; Annual Reports; Extension Reports, 1933-1940 1916-1939 1936-1939 (Box 35)
- Annual Reports; Budget Requests, 1930-1932 1955-1969 (Box 36)
- Department Reviews; Committee Reports; Market Bulletin; Variuos Reports; Market Administration, 1976-1977 1934-1966 1964 1947 - 1981 (Box 37)
- Department Budget Material, 1919-1944 (Box 38)
- Department Budget Material, 1923-1935 (Box 39)
- Farm Management Photo Album, ca. 1904-1909 (Volume 1)
  Photographs with descriptions from New York State farms, showing: crops, plowing, cattle, poultry, closeups of plants, grains, vegetable cross sections, farm buildings, and people working at the farms. Photos 1-928 inclusive
- Farm Management Photo Album, ca. 1909-1911 (Volume 2)
  Photographs with descriptions from New York State farms, showing: crops, plowing, machinery, cattle, poultry, closeups of plants, grains, farm buildings, students, and people working at the farms. Photos 929-1527 inclusive
- Farm Management Photo Album, ca. 1902, 1909-1919 (Volume 3)
  Photographs with descriptions from New York State farms, showing: Barn construction, crops, plowing, machinery, cattle, poultry, closeups of plants, grains, farm buildings, and people working at the farms. Photos 1-14, 1528-2707 inclusive
- Farm Management Photo Album, ca. 1918-1935 (Volume 4)
  Medium sized photograph and negative of Cabbage Books (Unattached)
  Photographs with descriptions from New York State farms, showing: markets, feed stores, crops, plowing, machinery, cattle, poultry, grains, farm buildings, and people working at the farms. Photos 2708-4375 inclusive
- Farm Crops Photo Album, ca. 1903-1906 (Volume 5)
  Photographs with descriptions and some negatives from New York State farms, showing: barn construction, crops, plowing, machinery, cattle, poultry, closeups of plants, cross sections of vegetables, grains, machinery,and harvesting. Photos 1-721 inclusive
- Farm Crops, photographs, 722-1063 inclusive, ca. 1906-1908 (Volume 6)
  Photographs with descriptions and some negatives from New York State farms, showing: barn construction, crops, plowing, machinery, cattle, poultry, closeups of plants, cross sections of vegetables, grains, machinery,farm buildings, people working at the farm, students, bread, cotton, and harvesting. Photos 722-1063 inclusive
- Day Book, 1910-1921 (Volume 7)
  A long list of names and items with numbers
- Department of Farm Management Scrapbook, ca. 1910-1917 (Volume 8)
  Contains farm management course syllabi, research papers, farm reports, farm club management association information, various programs, copies of examinations, survey cards
- Small scrapbook of photographs, Farms & Farm Practices, n.d.
- Volume-Agricultural Economics and Farm Management Course Material, 1921 (Box 41)
- Publication containing biographies of faculty and department history, 1992 (Box 41)
- Correspondence
  - Department of Agricultural Economics, E.G. Misner, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Agrifax Data Discussions, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Marketing Improvement Strategies, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Department of Animal Science (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Bailey, Liberty and Hyde Assistantships, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Bailey, Liberty and Hyde Professorships, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Biogas System, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Biometrics Unit Five Year Proposal, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Garry Christensen, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Royal Colle, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Rhodes Committee, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Current Economic Situation Information, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Dairy Promotion and Research Board, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Eastern Milk Producers, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - ESCOP Meeting, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - ESCOP Subcommittee on Special Initiatives, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 16-17)
  - Continental Grain Co. Gift to Agricultural Economics, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Extension Conferences, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Cooperative Extension Correspondence, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Cooperative Extension 75th Anniversary, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - The Empire State Food and Agricultural Leadership Institute, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Agricultural Leadership Program, 1983-1985 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Farm Financial Survey, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Farm Labor Management: Extension Program, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Farming Systems Research Symposium, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Genecco Proposals, 988 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Joint Council on Food and Agricultural Sciences, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Hatch Centennial Symposium, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Hatch Proposal Project Reviews, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Local Government, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Low Input Agriculture, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Diane Lufkin Correspondence, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Marketing and Management Workshops etc., 1986 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - May's/Sibley's Gift to Agricultural Economics, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Sukant Kumar Misra Correspondence, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Meetings and Communications with the Commissioner of Agriculture and Markets, New York State, 1984-1987 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- The Legacy of Charles H. Dyson DVD produced for the dedication of the School of Applied Economics and Management., 2012-10-01; DVD-1124